[
    {
        "question":"What is the actor's name of Warmaachine from IronMan 1 2008 ?",
        "choice":["Don Cheadle","Terrence Howard","Paul Bettany","Chad Bosman"],
        "answer":"Terrence Howard"
    },

    {
        "question":"What species is Star Lord's Mother ?",
        "choice":["Martian","Earthling","Asgardian","Nifleheim"],
        "answer":"Earthling"
    },

    {
        "question":"What is Deadpool mutant power?",
        "choice":["Teleportation","Mind Reader","Super Fast","Regeneration"],
        "answer":"Regeneration"
    },

    {
        "question":"What is Miles Morales ability ?",
        "choice":["Mind Reader","Breath in the water","Invisibility","Super Strong"],
        "answer":"Invisibility"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who is F.R.I.D.A.Y ?",
        "choice":["Tony's butler","Tony's AI","Tony's Assistant","Tony's wife"],
        "answer":"Tony's AI"
    },
    
    {
        "question":"What is Loki's father ?",
        "choice":["Odin","Thor","Laufey","Freiya"],
        "answer":"Laufey"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who is Steve Roger's enemy in Captain America: First Avenger?",
        "choice":["Red Hulk","Red Skull","Red Flag","Moon Knight"],
        "answer":"Red Skull"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who is Red Skull's Actor in Captain America ?",
        "choice":["Keanu Reeves","Hugo Weaving","Chris Pratt","Lydia Kandouw"],
        "answer":"Hugo Weaving"
    },

    {
        "question":"What is Thanos title ?",
        "choice":["Mad Purple","Mad Anger","Mad Titan","Mad Hunter"],
        "answer":"Mad Titan"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who killed Howard Stark ?",
        "choice":["Winter Knight","Winter Assasin","Winter Hunter","Winter Soldier"],
        "answer":"Winter Soldier"
    }

]